{
    "id": "b5dabcded3d44f48bcf9109b3891d9f6",
    "title": "American And British English Vocabulary",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "What is the dialling code for London?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fc47e66fe84e437789277ed45256bb91"
        },
        {
            "question": "Turn off the faucet when you are not using it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d991e5f04e824af0bc7f51b6476dd0bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thatâ€™s it. Can I have the check?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "998af75931df43d4b9bc96356a6405b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has bought a flat in upmarket London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "edcdd6be2a2a4758bb20b4812cf180ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got a torch?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "11619b6557a0475c8b4e516eaac18cf9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put the garbage in the bin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ec6ed6f7dd54f1ba51e9ec643bbbe2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "This car runs on petrol.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f886fce929b143b1ab2f661d638f0dc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had black pants on.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2cb7167bac6f4a1a9c8b0fc5208acd8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His nasty remarks made me angry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4f90fe5fc764b67b1b6b10234578ab6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who invented the zipper?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "British English",
                "American English"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a5ddf836e4a2457e94af33f7d5e82503"
        }
    ]
}